Mother, she's inside.
أمي ، إنها بالداخل.
Xinhuan, let Zi Yu tidy up first.
Xinhuan ، دع زي يو يرتب أولاً.
before I interrogate him.
قبل استجوابه.
Okay.
تمام.
Could it be...
هل من الممكن ذلك...
there must be something wrong with the way I open the door.
لابد أن هناك خطأ ما في الطريقة التي أفتح بها الباب.
Xin Huan.
شين هوان.
Why aren't you going in?
لماذا لا تدخل؟
Mother, let's go.
أمي ، دعنا نذهب.
What are you afraid of?
من ماذا انت خائف؟
I'll help you.
سوف اساعدك.
Your Highness!
صاحب السمو!
Mother!
الأم!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Sorry.
آسف.
We're discussing something.
نحن نناقش شيئًا ما.
You two women
أنتما امرأتان
barged in without notice.
اقتحم في دون سابق إنذار.
How inappropriate!
كم هو غير مناسب!
Xinhuan.
شينهوان.
Didn't you say the one in the brothel is...
ألم تقل أن من في بيت الدعارة ...
Father.
أب.
Prince Yu...
الأمير يو ...
Yu Xinhuan.
يو شينهوان.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
We...
نحن...
just to see
فقط لنرى
Is this where you can come?
هل هذا حيث يمكنك المجيء؟
Master, don't be angry.
سيدي ، لا تغضب.
I'll take Xinhuan away.
سآخذ Xinhuan بعيدا.
Let's talk at home.
لنتحدث في المنزل.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Go.
اذهب.
Close the door.
أغلق الباب.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
This is ridiculous.
هذا سخيف.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
My daughter
ابنتي
is naughty.
شقي.
Please forgive him.
من فضلك اغفر له.
It's okay.
حسنا.
Let's get down to business.
دعونا ننكب على العمل.
Come out.
يخرج.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What did you hear?
ماذا سمعت؟
So the grounding
لذا فإن التأريض
was ruined by Prince Yu again.
دمره الأمير يو مرة أخرى.
Right?
حق؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Zhao Da.
تشاو دا.
What can I do for you?
ما الذي يمكنني أن أفعله من أجلك؟
Find Sun Mei Niang,
البحث عن سون مي نيانغ ،
you must buy the Mountains and Rivers Map.
يجب عليك شراء خريطة الجبال والأنهار.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
The Mountains and Rivers painting
رسم الجبال والأنهار
is a treasure embroidered by Sun Mei Niang for ten years.
هو كنز طرزه صن مي نيانغ لمدة عشر سنوات.
I don't care if you kill her or rob her.
لا يهمني إذا قتلتها أو سرقتها.
Anyway, before Lantern Festival,
على أي حال ، قبل مهرجان الفوانيس ،
If you can't see the painting,
إذا كنت لا تستطيع رؤية اللوحة ،
you'll be beheaded.
سوف يتم قطع رأسك.
Sun Mei Niang is known as the best embroidery.
يُعرف Sun Mei Niang بأنه أفضل تطريز.
The original painting of the Mountains and Rivers Drawing
اللوحة الأصلية لرسم الجبال والأنهار
and embroideries are priceless.
والمطرزات لا تقدر بثمن.
Master Yu! Master Yu!
إتقان أنت!  إتقان أنت!
You're getting more capable now.
أنت تزداد قدرة الآن.
Now, you even dare to go to the brothel.
الآن ، حتى تجرؤ على الذهاب إلى بيت الدعارة.
I saved your face in front of others.
لقد حفظت وجهك أمام الآخرين.
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
How dare you yell at me?
كيف تجرؤ على الصراخ في وجهي؟
No, Madam.
لا سيدتي.
Let me explain.
دعني أوضح.
The Crown Prince asked me
سألني ولي العهد
to talk there.
للحديث هناك.
About what?
عن ما؟
go to the brothel?
اذهب الى بيت الدعارة؟
You don't know.
أنت لا تعرف.
The more dangerous the place is,
كلما كان المكان أكثر خطورة ،
the more dangerous it is.
كلما كان الأمر أكثر خطورة.
The more dangerous it is,
كلما كان الأمر أكثر خطورة ،
the easier it is to hide the truth.
أسهل إخفاء الحقيقة.
Master, Madam.
سيدتي.
Miss is back.
الآنسة عادت.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Father, Mother.
الأم الأب.
What are you looking at?
الى ماذا تنظرين؟
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Kneel down.
اركع للأسفل.
Mother!
الأم!
Master.
يتقن.
It's useless to call me mother.
لا فائدة من مناداتي يا أمي.
Say one more word.
قل كلمة أخرى.
You two kneel together.
أنتما الاثنان راكعا معا.
Kneel.
اركع.
Yu Xinhuan.
يو شينهوان.
That kind of place
هذا النوع من المكان
a place
مكان
for a girl?
لفتاة؟
Not only did you go alone,
لم تذهب وحدك فقط ،
you also took me with you.
أنت أيضا أخذتني معك.
Father, my mother and I...
أبي وأمي وأنا ...
We went to catch Prince Yu.
ذهبنا للقبض على الأمير يو.
I saw him hugging each other in the brothel.
رأيته يعانق بعضهما البعض في بيت الدعارة.
What?
لما؟
He's there for business.
إنه هناك من أجل العمل.
What business can he do in the brothel?
ما العمل الذي يمكنه القيام به في بيت الدعارة؟
How dare you talk back?
كيف تجرؤ على التحدث؟
Master, it's really
ماجستير ، إنه حقًا
It's indeed our fault.
إنه بالفعل خطأنا.
We misunderstood Ziyu.
لقد أسأنا فهم Ziyu.
Misunderstanding?
سوء فهم؟
Xinhuan, when you go back,
Xinhuan ، عندما تعود ،
apologize to Ziyu later.
اعتذر لـ Ziyu لاحقًا.
I...
أنا...
Do you hear me? Tomorrow morning court,
هل تسمعني؟  صباح الغد المحكمة ،
I'll ask Zi Yu
سأطلب زي يو
if you apologized.
إذا اعتذرت.
Mother.
الأم.
Just apologize.
فقط اعتذر.
Brother Zi Yu.
الأخ زي يو.
If Sixth Brother gets out of the house arrest,
إذا خرج الأخ السادس من الإقامة الجبرية ،
he will surely take revenge on you.
سوف ينتقم منك بالتأكيد.
How can you still eat?
كيف يمكنك أن تأكل؟
Everything is in accordance with the future.
كل شيء يتماشى مع المستقبل.
Why are you worried about the future?
لماذا أنت قلق بشأن المستقبل؟
You...
أنت...
Actually, you don’t need to worry.
في الواقع ، لا داعي للقلق.
If you want the sixth prince to be grounded,
إذا كنت تريد أن يتم تأريض الأمير السادس ،
just lend me something.
فقط اقرضني شيئا.
Master.
يتقن.
You're back, madam.
لقد عدت يا سيدتي.
Did she go back to her room?
هل عادت إلى غرفتها؟
Yes, but judging by her look,
نعم ، ولكن بالحكم من مظهرها ،
I'm afraid...
أنا خائف...
Thank you for today.
شكرا لهذا اليوم.
Zi Mu, find me a soft cushion later.
زي مو ، أجد لي وسادة ناعمة لاحقًا.
Then you can rest.
ثم يمكنك الراحة.
Yes, Master.
نعم سيدي.
Apologize, Prince Yu.
اعتذر يا أمير يو.
I'll apologize to you later.
سأعتذر لك لاحقا.
Madam, I'm back.
سيدتي ، لقد عدت.
My husband is back.
لقد عاد زوجي.
My father said
قال أبي
offended your conversation today.
أساء محادثتك اليوم.
to apologize to you.
للاعتذار لك.
Fine.
بخير.
You don't have to be so polite.
ليس عليك أن تكون مؤدبًا جدًا.
You even brought gifts.
حتى أنك أحضرت هدايا.
Tell me, what happened?
أخبرني بما حدث؟
I saw you hugging each other in the brothel.
رأيتك تعانق بعضكما البعض في بيت الدعارة.
But in a blink of an eye,
ولكن في غمضة عين ،
you're talking about business with my father and the Crown Prince?
تتحدثين عن العمل مع والدي وولي العهد؟
Well, I can't tell you.
حسنًا ، لا يمكنني إخبارك.
Will you tell me?
هل يمكنك اخباري؟
Since you want to know,
بما أنك تريد أن تعرف ،
I will tell you.
سأخبرك.
Actually, not long after Madam passed away,
في الواقع ، لم يمض وقت طويل على وفاة سيدتي ،
I saw the Crown Prince and father-in-law
رأيت ولي العهد ووالد زوجته
drinking and talking.
الشرب والحديث.
My father...
والدي...
And then?
وثم؟
Actually, you misunderstood.
في الواقع ، لقد أسيء فهمك.
The Crown Prince and father-in-law
ولي العهد ووالد زوجته
discuss
يناقش
the embroidery girl at Lantern Festival.
فتاة التطريز في مهرجان الفوانيس.
Lantern Festival?
مهرجان الفوانيس؟
There used to be many embroidery drawings in lantern festivals.
كان هناك العديد من رسومات التطريز في مهرجانات الفوانيس.
The top five embroiderers
أفضل خمس عارضات
can get His Majesty's grace
الحصول على نعمة صاحب الجلالة
and go to the place in the embroidery drawing.
وتذهب إلى المكان في رسم التطريز.
Anywhere.
في أى مكان.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
If you embroider Yaochi City,
إذا طرزت مدينة ياوتشي ،
you can travel to Yaochi City.
يمكنك السفر إلى مدينة Yaochi.
If you embroider the painting of mountains and rivers,
إذا طرزت لوحة الجبال والأنهار ،
you can go north to Tianshan
يمكنك الذهاب شمالا إلى تيانشان
and go south to Jiangsu and Zhejiang.
واتجه جنوبًا إلى Jiangsu و Zhejiang.
It's up to you to decide who to go out.
الأمر متروك لك لتقرر من ستخرج.
The royal family will pay for it. Okay.
ستدفع العائلة المالكة ثمنها.  تمام.